elliotsblog.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy | Elliot's Blog

**Privacy Policy Statement:**  
Top Notch Domains, LLC, a Nashua, NH based company is the owner of ElliotsBlog.com and has developed this Privacy Policy Statement to inform you about how we deal with privacy issues in relation to our website. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and on every page within our site.

**Overview**  
When you visit the our website, we can record certain information in relation to your visit such as your IP address or proxy server IP address, basic domain information, your Internet service provider information, the date and time of your visit, the length of your visit, the pages you have visited, the files you have downloaded, the number of times you have accessed our website, the website that referred you to us, links you clicked on to leave our website, your Internet browser information, your operating system information, your email address if you leave a comment, and possibly other non-identifiable details. This information is collected through the use of cookies via third party, password protected software..

**The Way We Use Information:**  
Top Notch Domains, LLC will only use the information it collects through this website to analyze our traffic and usage details, to monitor our website’s performance, and to re-contact someone who left their email address with a comment.

Top Notch Domains, LLC may provide aggregated statistical data to reputable third parties. This is not personally identifiable information.

Top Notch Domains, LLC will not disclose any personally identifiable, private information about you to a third party unless you have provided us with your consent or we are legally required to do so.

**Links to Other Webites**  
This website contains links to other websites. Top Notch Domains, LLC can not be held not responsible for the content or privacy practices of websites that are referenced or linked to in this website.

**Children Under 18**  
We do not believe our website has any materials that would be objectionable to children under the age of 18. If you find something that you believe is objectionable, please contact us at once using the contact information below.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access and ensure the security of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online that is under our control.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
Top Notch Domains, LLC retains the right to alter, modify or change the Privacy Policy at any time.

**How To Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about this, please call us at (610) 217-1642 or send us an email at DomainNames@gmail.com.
